Nikita Moiseienko

SUMMARY

As a node.js developer I specialize on building scalable and reliable back-end systems. I prefer to use a Test-Driven Development (TDD) approach in my work, or at least try to incorporate it as much as possible. I always enjoy improving my skills as a developer because I find programming inherently enjoyable.

EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer, 03/2022 - 01/2023 Selecto Global - Lviv, Ukraine

As a software developer at Selecto Global, I was responsible for developing and implementing software solutions for a variety of projects.

There are were a lot of projects that required real-time functionalities such as chats or location sharing.

Sometimes, there were new projects, so I had the possibility to build the backend part from scratch. But more often, there were existing projects on which I was involved in implementing new features, bug fixing, test coverage, optimizing database queries, writing new microservices to make compositions with already existing ones. https://nik-kita.github.io/selecto-reference-letter.pdf

Backend Developer. 03/2020 - 03/2022 Onix Systems - Kropivnitskii, Ukraine

During my tenure at Onix Systems, I gained my first commercial experience as a Node.js developer. I worked on various projects, including simple web projects, fitness applications, social platforms, and applications with complex integrations with external APIs and payment systems.

As I gained more experience, my responsibilities on these projects

Overall, my time at Onix Systems provided me with a solid foundation in Node.js development and exposed me to a variety of projects, technologies, and challenges.

Test Automation Engineer, 09/2019 - 03/2020 Onix Systems - Kropivnitskii, Ukraine

Automated existing test-cases for a fitness application, utilizing my skills in UI automation with Java and Selenium, as well as API automation using Java, RestAssured.

Artist of orchestra, 09/2018 - 06/2019

Lviv National Philarmonic - Lviv, Ukraine Artist of orchestra, 09/2017 - 05/2018



CONTACT

Address: Katowice, Poland **Phone:** 48506898737

Email: nik.moiseienko@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Typescript
- Javascript
- Node.is
- Nest.js
- Express
- Fastify
- Websocket
- Socket.io
- Postgres
- Mongodb
- GraphQl
- Stripe
- AWS
- GCP

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian: First Language

English:

В2

Upper Intermediate

Polish:

Α1

Beginner

EDUCATION

Master of Arts (Oboe Player) - National Music Academy, Lviv Ukraine, 2016

Additional courses, internships:

- "Backend development with PHP, Laravel" internship, Onix Systems, 2018
- "Test automation with Java" internship, Softserve Academy, 2018
- "Introduction to computer science" online cource, Harward Univercity, 2017

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

- Application for managing shops, customers, and delivery processes.
 Single backend with microservice architecture for 4 frontend apps.
 (Nest.js, Postgres, REST API, AWS S3, and Socket.io)
- Social app designed for groups to build activities around a person in need of help. Worked on developing chats and payment systems.
 (Nest.js, GCP, Stripe, Farebase)
- Sport app for coaches to purchase plans to manage their clients. (Express, Postgres, Stripe, GraphQL API).
- Social app similar to Instagram, focusing on updating and synchronizing users' posts feed. (Nest.js, MongoDB, Redis, Socket.io, Bull)
- Application that use REST and WS API of some crypto platforms to give some extra functional for spot-traders. (Nest.js, Postgres, Websocket)
- Driver app for managing delivery processes in real-time. (Nest.js, Postgres, Socket.io, Google map API, AWS es2, Nginx)